There is this form, can happen there, there is just, you can take within that, and I can still feel the field.
I am in the energy, this almost within this energy within this.
There is a, if in the truth, there is, you just let it, just sensations, just sensations running through like,
in all the absence of my body, I don't know, the start, the finish.
Just pulsing, just pulsing with the cosmos, just a feeling, this, this, this, this, this, this,
this, this, this created somewhere in between, I don't know, this, just the puls, the vibration,
and there is it, just a bundle of sensations and pulsing in between.
And, it felt really vast, it felt like somewhere in this space, just, I could feel one
with the galaxy, the stars.
It felt as if, this stars are also, I just, pulsing like this, just, just, just, you know.
But there is a sense of the coming back here, please, like, this is just very beautiful,
you know, but that was the, I felt, that I belong there, that is, that is, that is,
like, that is, this gives, I should be, you know.
That is smiling, I, I knew I was smiling, but I could not feed my smile, like, I,
this, maybe just joy, but, you know, this, this, right now, this,
Well, it's a mental illness, this disease is mentally connected, I think you're a bit over it.
What I felt in that was...
Honestly, there's no business here, there's nothing just just vibration running through.
I was lost in the sense, the pulse is the sensation, the vibration only does it.
Where is it just floating somewhere? I don't know here.
You know, it's very familiar, it's very familiar. It's not the first time.
I don't know if I'm able to do it in just my particular words.
Things are moving, it's just sensations are getting the form.
This is all happening within that.
I could feel, I lost you as well. I could not, I could not feel that I was in this particular space,
like this sense of space around the pond.
How do you describe that, but you spoke about it?
I'm trying my best.
It literally felt like, you know,
if I were to describe it visually, it just felt like stars and stars and stars
and the galaxy and the galaxy and the galaxy.
This is talking to each other, just pulsing and just being in sync with just...
Like, I'm just there within that space and just...
Like, I could feel like if something is going through here,
there's just some other stars vibrating with me and we're just in sync with just...
I don't know.
There's a number to it, there's this infinite...
this running through.
And the vibration can run through, there's no end to it, like it's just...
and somewhere in between those vibrations...